Academic Year: Information for New Students UP145
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Academic Year: Information for New Students
1952 -- 1993
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Dean of Student Affairs
UP145
0.75 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Academic Year, a handbook for entering undergraduate students. It included information on foundation and distribution degree requirements, student services, and rules and regulations.
From the 1955-56 edition, the title becomes, "Tufts University: Information for New Students," and from 1964-65 edition, "Tufts University: Supplementary Information for New Students." From 1966-67 it becomes, "Tufts University: Supplementary Information Entering Students," and in 1990 it becomes "The Academic Year: A Handbook for First-year Students." The Academic Year ceased publication in 1994, at which point the information was included in the Bulletin of Tufts University.
- Academic Year: Information for New Students, 1952 -- 1993; 1952 -- 1994; UP145.001; 0.75 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the Academic Year was a handbook for entering undergraduate students. It included information on foundation and distribution degree requirements, student services, and rules and regulations.
  From the 1955-56 edition, the title becomes, "Tufts University: Information for New Students," and from 1964-65 edition, "Tufts University: Supplementary Information for New Students." From 1966-67 it becomes, "Tufts University: Supplementary Information Entering Students," and in 1990 it becomes "The Academic Year: A Handbook for First-year Students."
  The Academic Year ceased publication in 1994, at which point the information was included in the Bulletin of Tufts University.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts College: Information for New Students, 1952 -- 1955; UP145.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University: Information for New Students, 1955 -- 1961; UP145.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University: Information for New Students, 1961 -- 1965; UP145.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University: Supplementary Information for Entering Students, 1966 -- 1969; UP145.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - The Academic Year, 1986 -- 1987; UP145.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - The Academic Year, 1987 -- 1988; UP145.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - The Academic Year, 1989 -- 1990; UP145.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - The Academic Year, 1990 -- 1991; UP145.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - The Academic Year, A Handbook for New Students, 1991 -- 1992; UP145.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - The Academic Year, A Handbook for New Students, 1992 -- 1993; UP145.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - The Academic Year, Class of 1984, 1980 -- 1981; UP145.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - The Academic Year, Class of 1985, 1981 -- 1982; UP145.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - The Academic Year, Class of 1986, 1982 -- 1983; UP145.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - The Academic Year, Class of 1987, 1983 -- 1984; UP145.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - The Academic Year, Class of 1988, 1984 -- 1985; UP145.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - The Academic Year, Class of 1989, 1985 -- 1986; UP145.001.003.00006 (Box 3)